<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IndyFitCalculator</string>
    
    <string-array name="calculator_names">
        <item>Body Mass Index (BMI)</item>
        <item>Ideal Body Weight (IBW)</item>
        <item>Basal Metabolic Rate (BMR)</item>
        <item>Calorie Requirement</item>
        <item>Body Fat Percentage (BFP)</item>
        <item>Body Surface Area (BSA)</item>
        <item>Carbohyrdates Requirements</item>
        <item>Protein Requirements</item>
        <item>Fat Requirements</item>
        <item>Total Daily Energy Expenditure (TDEE)</item>
        <item>Waist-to-Hip Ratio</item>
        <item>Body Adiposity Index (BAI)</item>
        <item>Blood Alcohol Concentration</item>
        <item>Lean Body Mass Assessment (LBM)</item>
        <item>Fat Free Mass Index (FFMI)</item>
        <item>Maximum Heart Rate (MHR)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="calculator_desc">
        <item>
            Body Mass Index is a screening tool that can indicate whether a person is underweight
            or if they have a healthy weight, excess weight, or obesity.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ideal Body Weight tests help to measure the actual weight that people need to
            maintain for maximal health.
        </item>
        <item>
            Basal Metabolic Rate test helps to estimate the amount of energy your body burns
            at rest daily.
        </item>
        <item>
            Calorie Requirement Calculator is used to estimate the number of calories a person
            needs to consume each day.
        </item>
        <item>
            Body Fat Percentage Calculator is used to estimate total body fat percentage based
            on a specific formula.
        </item>
        <item>
            Body Surface Area measure or calculator helps to estimate the surface area of a human body.
        </item>
        <item>
            Carbohyrdates Requirements Calculator helps to estimates the required amounts of
            carbohydrates that a person needs each day.
        </item>
        <item>
            Protein Requirements Calculator helps to estimates the required amounts of
            protein that a person needs each day.
        </item>
        <item>
            Fat Requirements Calculator helps to estimates the required amounts of
            fat that a person needs each day.
        </item>
        <item>
            Total Daily Energy Expenditure is an estimation of how many calories a person burns per day when exercise is taken into account.
        </item>
        <item>
            Waist-to-Hip Ratio is a quick measure of fat distribution (especially on waist, hips, and buttocks) that may help indicate a person's overall health. It also helps to measure abdominal obesity.
        </item>
        <item>
            Body Adiposity Index is a practical anthropometric method used to measure body fat percentage.
        </item>
        <item>
            Blood Alcohol Concentration refers to the amount of alcohol present in the bloodstream.
        </item>
        <item>
            Lean Body Mass Assessment determines a person's estimated lean body mass (LBM) based on body weight, height, gender, and age.
        </item>
        <item>
            Fat Free Mass Index is an alternative to body mass index, which helps in estimates a person's muscle mass.
        </item>
        <item>
            Maximum Heart Rate is most accurately measured using a cardiac stress test, which
            involves measuring a person's heart function (including heart rate) at periodically
            increasing levels of exercise.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>